Guide to the Horace Dwight Taft Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Physics Files, 1947-1983; Series III; 12.25' (31 boxes)
  - ELREC, 1968, undated (Box 71, Folder 273)
  - WCAL, 1975, undated (Box 71, Folder 274)
  - HIST, 1966, undated (Box 71, Folder 275)
  - ZCHIST, 1969 (Box 71, Folder 276)
  - ANGCAL, 1967, undated (Box 71, Folder 277-278)
  - THIST, 1968, undated (Box 71, Folder 279-280)
  - PEPR operating instructions, 1970 (Box 71, Folder 281)
  - PRED, 1965, undated (Box 71, Folder 282)
  - Fortran PEPR, 1964, undated (Box 71, Folder 283)
  - CALEL, undated (Box 71, Folder 284)
  - Fortran Boxout, 1965, undated (Box 71, Folder 285)
  - GETSET, undated (Box 72, Folder 286)
  - CPCAL, undated (Box 72, Folder 287)
  - New ELREC, 1968, undated (Box 72, Folder 288)
  - Displays, undated (Box 72, Folder 289)
  - Miscellaneous material, undated (Box 72, Folder 290)
  - DACAL, 1966, undated (Box 72, Folder 291)
  - Output format. PDP 1, undated (Box 72, Folder 292)
  - VEE program, 1964-1965, undated (Box 72, Folder 293-294)
  - SIGFIT, undated (Box 72, Folder 295)
  - K2-d experiment
    - Deuterium, 1965-1969, undated (Box 72, Folder 296)
    - FLUX + 6, 1969, undated (Box 72, Folder 297)
    - K* mass [difference?], 1962-1971, undated (Box 72, Folder 298)
    - K1 regeneration, undated (Box 72, Folder 299)
    - Ko Ld interactions from 1 to 10 GeV/c, 1976 (Box 73, Folder 300)
    - Ko 2 experiment, 1964-1965, undated (Box 73, Folder 301)
    - K2 experiment, 1964-1965, undated (Box 73, Folder 302)
    - K2 experiment, 1965, undated (Box 73, Folder 303)
    - K2 field, 1968-1970, undated (Box 73, Folder 304-305)
    - K2 hardware, 1969-1970, undated (Box 73, Folder 306)
    - K2 Monte Carlo, undated (Box 73, Folder 307)
    - K2 theory, 1959-1970, undated (Box 73, Folder 308-309)
    - K2-d proposal, undated (Box 74, Folder 310)
    - K2-d: Run, 1970-1971, undated (Box 74, Folder 311)
    - Miscellaneous, 1964-1968, undated (Box 74, Folder 312)
    - Proposal, 1967-1970, undated (Box 74, Folder 313-314)
    - Short lifetime physics collaboration, 1981, undated (Box 74, Folder 315)
    - Stanford Linear Accelerator Center presentation, 1970, undated (Box 74, Folder 316)
    - Stanford Linear Accelerator Center proposal, 1969-1970, undated (Box 74, Folder 317)
    - Transparencies, undated (Box 74, Folder 318)
  - Graphs, 1953 (Box 74, Folder 319)
  - Hydro II and Cloudy III, 1957-1959 (Box 74, Folder 320)
  - Insulation, 1956-1957, undated (Box 74, Folder 321)
  - Miscellaneous material, 1956-1958, undated (Box 75, Folder 322)
  - K- planarization, undated (Box 75, Folder 323)
  - K-, 1959, undated (Box 75, Folder 324)
  - Σ+ production (I spin), undated (Box 75, Folder 325)
  - Meson production at high energies, undated (Box 75, Folder 326)
  - Kinematics and spectra, undated (Box 75, Folder 327)
  - Kinematics, undated (Box 75, Folder 328)
  - Multiple scattering, undated (Box 75, Folder 329)
  - Stat model and I spin, undated (Box 75, Folder 330)
  - K- production, undated (Box 75, Folder 331)
  - 2D K- stack, 1957 (Box 75, Folder 332)
  - I spin, undated (Box 75, Folder 333)
  - Measurement of field, undated (Box 75, Folder 334)
  - Meetings, undated (Box 75, Folder 335)
  - Midwestern Universities Research Association: FFAG, 1952-1954 (Box 75, Folder 336)
  - Pencil beam, 1956, undated (Box 75, Folder 337)
  - π+ beams, undated (Box 75, Folder 338)
  - Pion scattering data, 1951-1954, undated (Box 75, Folder 339)
  - Pseudite, 1954, undated (Box 75, Folder 340)
  - Range distribution, undated (Box 75, Folder 341)
  - References, undated (Box 75, Folder 342)
  - Tubes, undated (Box 75, Folder 343)
  - Wire, 1957 (Box 75, Folder 344)
  - Pion production by pions, 1956, undated (Box 75, Folder 345-346)
  - Programs, 1958, undated (Box 75, Folder 347)
  - KICK, undated (Box 76, Folder 348)
  - KICK correspondence, 1958-1960 (Box 76, Folder 349)
  - π scattering, undated (Box 76, Folder 350)
  - Bubbles, undated (Box 76, Folder 351)
  - Comparison of the Results Obtained by Direct Solution and Schröclinger Perturbation Methods for the Quantum-Mechanical Problem of a Particle in Two Adjacent Potential Minima, undated (Box 76, Folder 352)
  - Miscellaneous material, Undated, 1982-1983 (Box 76, Folder 353-355)
  - PDP 10 system, undated (Box 76, Folder 356)
  - E 630 director's review, 1980-1981, undated (Box 76, Folder 357)
  - DOE presentation, 1981-1982, undated (Box 76, Folder 358)
  - DOE visit, 1981 (Box 76, Folder 359)
  - DOE site visit, 1979 (Box 77, Folder 360)
  - Dispersion relations, undated (Box 77, Folder 361)
  - Phase space, undated (Box 77, Folder 362)
  - Vertex agreement, undated (Box 77, Folder 363)
  - Shutt chamber parameters, undated (Box 77, Folder 364-365)
  - Matrix package, 1956-1963, undated (Box 77, Folder 366-367)
  - Old programs
    - Optical parameters, undated (Box 77, Folder 368)
    - Minimizing routines, 1961-1963, undated (Box 77, Folder 369)
    - New Minfern write-up, undated (Box 77, Folder 370)
  - Imported programs
    - COSMIC, 1967 (Box 77, Folder 371-372)
    - Optical parameters, 1963 (Box 78, Folder 373)
  - Magnetic Field
    - 80" B field: part II, 1964-1965, undated (Box 78, Folder 374)
    - 80" B field, 1964, undated (Box 78, Folder 375)
  - Miscellaneous material, 1957, 1964-1970 (Box 78, Folder 376)
  - Weak interactions (Willis), 1965 (Box 78, Folder 377)
  - Notes: pp. 1-22, undated (Box 78, Folder 378)
  - Notes: pp. 23-141, undated (Box 78, Folder 379)
  - Lectures: pp. 1-91, 1965 (Box 78, Folder 380)
  - Lectures: pp. 92-141, 1965 (Box 78, Folder 381)
  - Physics 127a: notes, [1966?] (Box 78, Folder 382)
  - Kinematics, undated (Box 78, Folder 383)
  - Scattering theory, undated (Box 78, Folder 384)
  - Phase space, undated (Box 78, Folder 385)
  - Dalitz: Brookhaven National Laboratory, 1961, undated (Box 78, Folder 386)
  - Dalitz and τ mesons, undated (Box 79, Folder 387)
  - π - µ decays, undated (Box 79, Folder 388)
  - Cyclotron status reports, 1953-1955 (Box 79, Folder 389-391)
  - Annual Report on Study of Interaction of High Energy Particles With Matter, 1957-1959 (Box 79, Folder 392)
  - Beams, 1964-1965 (Box 79, Folder 393)
  - Bubble chamber photograph documentation, 1958-1961 (Box 79, Folder 394)
  - Bubble chamber experiments (Propane), undated (Box 79, Folder 395)
  - Bubble chambers, undated (Box 79, Folder 396)
  - Cambridge Electron Accelerator, 1956-1957 (Box 79, Folder 397)
  - Cerenkou effect, undated (Box 79, Folder 398)
  - x2 surface (Garsy), undated (Box 79, Folder 399)
  - Circuits, 1954, undated (Box 79, Folder 400)
  - Ξ o, undated (Box 79, Folder 401)
  - Coulomb functions, undated (Box 79, Folder 402)
  - Distortion (Box 79, Folder 403)
  - nD production, undated (Box 79, Folder 404)
  - Electromagnetic theory, undated (Box 79, Folder 405)
  - Epoxy adhesives, 1954-1956 (Box 79, Folder 406)
  - Experimental set-up, undated (Box 79, Folder 407)
  - Field theory, 1958, undated (Box 80, Folder 408)
  - Maryland talk, 1959-1960, undated (Box 80, Folder 409)
  - Σ - high field, 1957 (Box 80, Folder 410)
  - ppM matrix, 1961, undated (Box 80, Folder 411)
  - CULL, 1961, undated (Box 80, Folder 412)
  - Alvarez group: orbit system, 1960 (Box 80, Folder 413)
  - Yale machine, 1959-1960, undated (Box 80, Folder 414)
  - BIGDI, 1979 (Box 80, Folder 415)
  - LEGENDRE POLY. FIT, undated (Box 80, Folder 416)
  - Miscellaneous material, undated (Box 80, Folder 417)
  - Least squares and max likelihood, undated (Box 80, Folder 418)
  - Miscellaneous material, undated (Box 80, Folder 419)
  - π π graphs, undated (Box 80, Folder 420)
  - [Telegeh + HPS?], [1965?] (Box 80, Folder 421)
  - Miscellaneous material, Undated, 1955 (Box 80, Folder 422-423)
  - Pion production in [á½´-á½´?], undated (Box 80, Folder 424)
  - K+ + d, undated (Box 80, Folder 425)
  - Photo-meson production, undated (Box 81, Folder 426)
  - Polarization, undated (Box 81, Folder 427)
  - Durand, undated (Box 81, Folder 428)
  - Delta rays, undated (Box 81, Folder 429)
  - Clebsch-Gordon, undated (Box 81, Folder 430)
  - JET articles, 1979 (Box 81, Folder 431)
  - Miscellaneous material, undated (Box 81, Folder 432)
  - E 69: small angle scattering experiment, 1979 (Box 81, Folder 433)
  - Streamer chamber collaboration, 1975 (Box 81, Folder 434)
  - Unidentified, undated (Box 81, Folder 435)
  - YAPR papers, 1960, undated (Box 81, Folder 436)
  - HVMULT for E630, 1981 (Box 81, Folder 437)
  - Fast on-line electronics, 1979-1982 (Box 81, Folder 438)
  - Miscellaneous material, 1966-1979, undated (Box 81, Folder 439)
  - Miscellaneous computer materials, 1967, 1975, undated (Box 81, Folder 440)
  - Computer printouts, 1976-1983 (Box 82, Folder 441-444)
  - Computer printouts, 1981 (Box 83, Folder 445-447)
  - Computer printouts, 1980-1982 (Box 84, Folder 448-450)
  - Computer tapes, 1973, 1982 (Box 85, Folder 451-452)